madewithvuejs.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Statement - Made with Vue.js

## At A Glance

**Who is responsible for the collection of data on madewithvuejs.com?**  
Nifty Software e.U. is responsible for the data collection and storage. Our contact data can be found in the Imprint.

**How do we collect your data?  **  
Primarily we collect data that you consciously give to us, f.ex. with subscribing to our newsletter, by sending us an e-mail to get your project added or by booking a package to feature your project.

Other data will be automatically collected when you visit madewithvuejs.com. These are mainly technical data like your browser, OS or the time of your visit. This happens automatically and helps us to see how we can improve our site. These data will never be linked to your personal data (like f.ex. your e-mail address that you gave us when subscribing to our newsletter). We can not (and do not want to) create a profile of you and your browsing habits.

To keep madewithvuejs.com alive, we also use Affiliate & Ad Services, that may store the timestamp of your visit, your IP-address and a cookie.

**How do we use your data?  **  
We use statistics to further develop our website and to make sure to be able to deliver it without issue. Your e-mail address will only be used to answer your questions, send you our newsletter (if you consciously signed up for it). Your personal and company data will only be used to create an invoice for purchased feature packages or provide the purchased services.

Some data will be processed by Third Parties. This is limited to our Newsletter Provider MailChimp (see 2 below), the tools we use to handle the purchase of feature packages (TypeForm and Stripe, see 1 below) and our Webspace Provider (Digital Ocean, see 1 below). We only share necessary data to provide a specific service with those parties (f.ex. only your e-mail address to send you a newsletter).

We will not share your data with any other third parties and we won't use it for anything else ourselves. If you personally write us an e-mail, your address will be handled only by us, confidentially.

**What are your rights?**  
You have the right to request information about origin, recipients and purpose of your data free of charge at any time. You can demand correction, locking or deletion of your data – just send us an informal e-mail.

In case we don’t comply with your request, you have the right to complain at the responsible regulating authority. Of course, it’s in our interest to guarantee your personal data privacy. If you have any questions please feel free to contact us.

## Legal Notes

**Scope**  
This privacy statement informs the user about the type, the extent and the purpose of the collection and usage of personal data through the responsible provider Nifty Software e.U. - Trautmannsdorf 178, A-8343 Bad Gleichenberg, Mail: [armin@nifty.at](mailto:armin@nifty.at), Tel: 0660/5646697 on this website.

The legal basis for privacy can be found in the Data Protection Act (Datenschutzgesetz, DSG) and the Telemedia Act (Telemediengesetz, TMG).

**Withdrawal, Change, Permissions & Updating of Data**  
The user has the right to be informed about the personal data saved by us upon request free of charge. Additionally, the user has the right to request the correction of incorrect data, suspension or deletion of his personal data, as far as we are not obliged by law to preserve these records.

### 1\. Collection and Use of Personal Information

**Access-Data / Server-Logfiles**  
Our Webspace Provider is collecting data about every access to the offered services through server log files for us. We use the services of the provider Digital Ocean, LLC, 101 Avenue of the Americas, New York, New York 10013, with whom we have closed a Data Processing Agreement.

We trust in the reliability and the IT- and data security of Digital Ocean. Digital Ocean is certified under the US-EU-Data Privacy Convention “[Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG)” and is therefore obligated to comply with EU data privacy requirements.

The processed data includes the name of the visited webpage or document, date and time of the visit, the amount of data transmitted, whether our server successfully delivered a web page, browser type and version, the OS of the user, referrer URLs, IP-addresses and the inquiring provider.

We are using these data solely for the operation, security and optimization of the service, but we reserve our right to review the data to explore any indication of illegal usage.

**Contact Information**  
When contacting us through the contact form or via e-mail, your data will be stored to handle the request or any further inquiries.

**Cookies**  
This website uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Cookies can be read by the Website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the webpage, or a unique identification number so that the Website can “remember” you on your return visit.

Most browsers let their users decide on how cookies should be handled. You can find these options in the settings of your browser. Please notice that the usage of our services and the user experience could suffer from preventing our website to set a cookie.

You can manage many cookies of ad companies through the US site <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or the EU site <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>.

**Data Processing for Business Purposes (Feature Packages)  
** We process the data of our contractual partners and other clients to fulfil contractual services. The processed data, the purpose, extent, purpose and the requirement of processing are governed by the underlying contractual relationship.

We only process data that are required to conclude the contract and to fulfil the contractual services: The master data of our contractual partners (f.ex. names & addresses), contact data (f.ex. e-mail addresses) as well as contractual data (f.ex. the purchased ad packages, communication in the context of the purchase,..);

We don’t directly process any payment data. Your payment data (f.ex. account data) will only be processed by our external payment provider Stripe (see chapter External Payment Provider). We don’t have access to any of your payment details (f.ex. your credit card number) and only get a payment confirmation or the information that your payment has failed.

These data will not be shared with other third party services than those listed below, except it's explicitly necessary to fulfil a contractual service.

We don’t process other data, except when they’re part of our contractual service (f.ex. you specifically request us to publish them alongside your project data).

**\- TypeForm**  
We use the services of TypeForm (TYPEFORM, S.L., Bac de Roda 163, 08018 Barcelona, Spain) to provide you with a convenient way to book our feature packages. Data entered via our Booking Forms (master data, contact data) will be processed by them. These data will not be shared with other Third Party Services and are only accessible to us.

The payment within the TypeForm forms is handled via Stripe (see chapter External Payment Provider) and will not be stored by TypeForm.

You can consult their privacy policy for further information: <https://admin.typeform.com/to/dwk6gt>

**\- External Payment Provider**  
We are using an external payment provider to receive your payments for Feature Packages: Stripe Payments Europe Ltd, Block 4, Harcourt Centre, Harcourt Road, Dublin 2, Irland.

We trust in the reliability and the IT- and data security of Stripe. Stripe is certified under the US-EU-Data Privacy Convention “[Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG)” and is therefore obligated to comply with EU data privacy requirements.

Furthermore, we closed a “Data-Processing-Agreement” with Stripe. This contract ensures that Stripe is protecting the data of our users, to only process data at our orders and in accordance with their data privacy statement and especially not to share data with third parties.

You can consult their privacy policy for further information: <https://stripe.com/at/privacy>.

**Comments**  
If you leave a comment on our site, we do not only store your comment but also information about the date and time of you commenting, your e-mail address, the name and website URL you entered voluntarily.

**\- Preservation duration of Comments**   
The comments will be stored until the commented content is removed from our site or the comment must be deleted for legal reasons (f.ex. abusive comments).

**\- Legal Basis**  
The storage of comments is based on your consent (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR). You can revoke your consent at any time by sending the provider an informal request. The legality of any data processing that has already happened at the time of you revoking your consent remains intact.

### 2\. Newsletter

With our newsletter, we inform you about new and popular Vue.js projects on our site and other services related to our site.

If you want to receive our newsletter, we need a valid e-mail address. We also need information to ensure that you own the e-mail address with which you are subscribing / that the owner is consenting to receive our newsletter. Other data will not be saved. These data are only used for sending newsletters and will not be passed on to third parties.

With the subscription to our newsletter, we will store your IP address and the timestamp of your subscription. Storing this information is important to prove that the owner of the e-mail address gave his consent to receive our newsletter.

You can revoke your consent to our storing of your data and to receive our newsletter at any time free of charge. You can unsubscribe through a link in every issue of our newsletter, through managing your preferences in your profile or by sending us an informal request.

The distribution of our newsletters is carried out by “MailChimp”, a newsletter tool of the US company Rocket Science Group, LLC, 675 Ponce De Leon Ave NE #5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA.

The e-mail addresses of our newsletter subscribers, as well as the data collected as described above, will be stored on the servers of MailChimp in the USA. MailChimp is using this information to distribute and analyze our newsletters according to our orders. In addition, MailChimp is authorized to use our data to optimize and improve their services, f.ex. for the technical optimization of the distribution of newsletters. MailChimp is not using the data of our subscribers to send them newsletters about their services or to share them with third parties.

We trust in the reliability and the IT- and data security of MailChimp. MailChimp is certified under the US-EU-Data Privacy Convention “[Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG)” and is therefore obligated to comply with EU data privacy requirements. Furthermore, we closed a “[Data-Processing-Agreement](http://mailchimp.com/legal/forms/data-processing-agreement/)” with MailChimp. This contract ensures that MailChimp is protecting the data of our users, to only process data at our orders and in accordance with their data privacy statement and especially not to share data with third parties. You can read the data privacy statement of MailChimp [on their website](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

The newsletter issues contain a so-called „web-beacon“, which is a pixel-sized file that will be called by MailChimp’s servers upon opening the newsletter. Through this beacon, technical data like your browser and OS, as well as your IP address and the timestamp of you opening the newsletter can be accessed and stored by MailChimp. This information is used for the optimization and improvement of the service.

These data also include whether the newsletter has been opened, when it has been opened and which links got clicked. This information can be linked to the personal data of our subscribers for technical reasons, although it is not in our interest, nor in the interest of MailChimp to observe or analyze individual users. These statistics are used to gain insights into the preferences of our subscribers to provide them with content that is useful to them.

### 3\. Analytics Tools, Advertising & Affiliate Programs

**Google Analytics**  
Our website is using Google Analytics, an analytics tool from Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics is using cookies – small text files that are saved on your computer and that allow the analysis of the usage of our site. The information gathered by the cookie is sent to Google’s servers in the USA and stored there.

Your IP-address is anonymized. Your full IP-address will not be sent to Google’s servers in the USA, except in exceptional cases where the address will be sent first, and then shortened before it’s stored. According to our orders, Google is using this information to analyze the usage of our website, create reports about the user’s activity and to offer other services that are related to our user’s activity and the usage of the web.

Your IP address will not be consolidated with other data stored on Google’s servers. You can prevent us and Google Analytics setting a cookie via your browser settings. Please notice that the usage of our services and the user experience could suffer from preventing our website to set a cookie. If you want to prevent Google from setting any cookies on your computer through activating the following browser-plugin: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

For further information about the usage of data for advertising purposes, setting- and your options to opt-out of the transmission of your data, read the information on Google’s Websites:  
<https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/partners?hl=en> (“How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps”) <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en> (“Advertising”),  
<http://www.google.de/settings/ads?hl=en> and <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences?hl=en>  (“Control the information Google uses to show you ads”)

Alternatively, or if you’re using a mobile browser, click on this link to prevent Google from gathering data on our website. With clicking this link, an opt-out cookie will be saved on your device. If you delete your cookies, you will need to click on the link again to stay opted-out.

**Amazon Affiliate Program**  
Armin Ulrich participates in the affiliate program of Amazon EU, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.de / amazon.com / amazon.uk. Amazon uses cookies to be able to know where the orders originated. Among other things, Amazon can detect that you clicked the affiliate link on our website.

For further information about the data usage by Amazon, please see their [privacy statement](http://www.amazon.de/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=3312401).

**Carbon Ads**  
Our website displays advertising in the form of text links, image links and banner ads by „Carbon Ads“ (Carbon). Carbon uses cookies – small text files that are saved on your computer – to analyze the use of their advertisements.

The information stored in the cookie (your IP address, but not data like your e-mail address, name or other identifying data) is sent and stored on Carbon’s servers. This information can be accessed by co-contractors of Carbon.

Most browsers let their users decide on how cookies should be handled. You can find these options in the settings of your browser. For blocking the ads by Carbon, you need to block cookies set by the domain carbonads.net. Please notice that the usage of our services and the user experience could suffer from preventing our website to set a cookie.

For further information about the data usage by Carbon Ads, please see their [privacy statement](https://carbonads.net/privacy.php).

**Creative Tim**  
Armin Ulrich participates in the affiliate program of Creative Tim, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to creative-tim.com. Creative Tim uses cookies to be able to know where the orders originated. Among other things, Creative Tim can detect that you clicked the affiliate link on our website.

For further information about the data usage by Creative Tim, please see their [privacy statement](https://www.creative-tim.com/privacy).

### 4\. Social Media

**Sharing Content via Social Media**  
The content on our site can be shared in a way that complies with data privacy. The Share-Buttons on our website will not transmit any of your data to social networks like Facebook, Twitter or Pinterest before you click on them. Social Media is not able to create a profile of your browsing habits.

## Privacy Statement Changes

We may change this Privacy Statement from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Statement. Your continued use of the Website after any change in this Privacy Statement will constitute your acceptance of such change.

_last edited: 22.05.2018_
